discountschoolsupply.com 2018-06-30

# School Supplies, Classrooms & Teaching Store | Discount School Supply®

This Privacy Policy discloses the self-regulated privacy practices of Excelligence Learning Corporation (Excelligence®), sole owner of DiscountSchoolSupply.com. By posting this policy, we want you to understand what information we gather about you, how we use it, and the safeguards we have in place to protect it. 

If you have questions/comments regarding this posted Privacy Policy, please contact our Webmaster: 

[Webmaster@DiscountSchoolSupply.com](mailto:Webmaster@DiscountSchoolSupply.com) (Subject: Privacy Policy Question).

**Information Collection and Use**  
Excelligence® Learning Corporation is the sole owner of the information collected on this website. We collect information from site users at several different places on this site. Other than as disclosed in this policy, we will not sell or rent this information or share it with a third party. 

We may collect personal information about you on this site to service your account and to personalize your experience. For example, we may collect your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, or credit card number when you voluntarily submit the information to us during the checkout process or when you request a catalog via our site. 

We use your information to process and complete your order and to inform you of your order status. We also use your information to register you as a user of our site or to provide you with services, such as access to your order history. We also collect personal information from you if you choose to subscribe to our emails or participate in giveaways, contests, surveys, or in connection with comments, activity ideas or other content you post on our site. 

We may also collect information about you, such as the size of your classroom, how often you purchase certain items, etc., that you provide to us on our site. Non-personally-identifiable information may also be collected from you through “cookies” and “pixel tags,” which are explained in the next section of this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, we may collect demographic information about you from third parties, such as your USPS postal address designation. We use this information to provide you with the most appropriate services and relevant offers from us. 

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**  
A “pixel tag” is a clear GIF image used in combination with cookies to pass measured information to a third party. 

Cookies are a repository of measured values set on your computer to monitor your behavior while visiting the web site. The cookies are required for personalization features and for our shopping cart and checkout to function properly. 

By allowing cookies, you allow us to preserve some of your account information, including your zip code and your customer ID. Cookies save you time when using our website in the future because they allow us to recognize you when you return to our site and to provide you with a personalized experience that we feel will be of value to you. The cookies that are configured by our website do not contain any personally- identifying information, such as your name or your credit card number. 

We and our third-party service providers use cookies on our site to identify, for example, your IP address, type of browser, and specific web pages through which you click. This data is collected automatically and is used to help us look for ways to improve our site and your experience on it. 

**DiscountSchoolSupply.com and "Cookies"**

Cookies are small files stored on your PC that identify you to our site. DiscountSchoolSupply.com uses cookies to personalize your shopping experience, making it more efficient and pleasant. Most browsers have a default setting to accept cookies automatically; however, your browser may have been configured not to accept cookies.

Your web browser is not currently configured to accept "cookies." In order to shop or register on DiscountSchoolSupply.com, you must be able to accept cookies. Check below for instructions on enabling cookies. If you don’t see your browser listed, please refer to the Help function for your browser.

If you cannot enable cookies, or choose not to, please call 1–800–627-2829 to place your order or get additional assistance.

* * *

Instructions may vary based on platform, browser and browser version. These instructions are approximate. For exact instruction refer to your browser’s help file or your browser’s manufacturer.

**Microsoft Internet Explorer 7.x, Windows**

  1. On the Tools menu, click Internet Options.
  2. On the Privacy tab, move the slider to Low or Accept All Cookies.
  3. Click OK.

For more information, visit the Microsoft Web site and read this article:  

**Microsoft Internet Explorer 6.x, Windows**

  1. On the Tools menu, click Internet Options.
  2. On the Privacy tab, move the slider to Low or Accept All Cookies.
  3. Click OK.

For more information, visit the Microsoft Web site and read this article:  

**Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.x, Windows**

  1. On the Tools menu, click Internet Options.
  2. On the Security tab, click the Custom Level button.
  3. Scroll down to the Cookies section.
  4. Set "Allow cookies that are stored on your computer" to "Enable."
  5. Set "Allow per–session cookies" to "Enable."
  6. Click OK.

For more information, visit the Microsoft Web site and read this article:  
[How to Set and Customize Cookies Settings in Internet Explorer](http://support.microsoft.com/default.aspx?scid=kb;EN-US;196955)

**Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.x, Macintosh**

  1. On the Explorer menu, select Preferences.
  2. Under the Receiving Files option, select Cookies.
  3. Under "When receiving cookies:" select Never Ask.
  4. Click OK.

For more information, visit the Microsoft Web site and read this article:  

**Safari**

  1. On the Safari menu, click Preferences.
  2. Click the Security icon.
  3. In the Accept Cookies selection box, choose Always.
  4. Close the security window.

For more information, visit the Apple Web site and read this article:  

**Mozilla**

  1. On the Edit menu, click Preferences.
  2. In the Privacy & Security category, choose Cookies.
  3. Click the radio button next to "Enable all cookies."
  4. Click OK.

For more information, visit the Mozilla Web site and read this article:  

**Firefox**

  1. On the Tools menu, click Options.
  2. Select the Privacy category.
  3. Expand the Cookies options on the right.
  4. Select Enable Cookies.
  5. Click OK.

**Information Security**  
We take safety measures to safeguard your personal information. When you submit sensitive information through our website, the information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as name, address, or credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected with the current industry standard encryption protocol known as “secure socket layer” or “SSL.” While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon (as shown here ) appears on the bottom or top of your web browsers. Secure web pages also have URL’s (Uniform Resource Locator) that start with https:// instead of http://. To learn more about SSL, visit 

[http://www.verisign.com/](http://www.verisign.com/). 

In addition to using SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take reasonable measures to protect your information off-line. Other than information that is shared (as described in the “Sharing Information” section below), your personally-identifiable information referenced above is restricted in our offices. Within our offices, access to your information is granted to our employees/auditors for the sole purpose of performing specific jobs that relate to our business. (For example, a personal service manager may need to access your contact information.) Employees are instructed on the importance we place on privacy, and when new policies are implemented, we stress the steps employees should take to ensure that our customers’ information is safeguarded. Finally, the servers on which we store personal information are kept in a secure environment, accessible only to authorized employees. 

We also work with security company, McAfee® to add an additional layer to our security protocol. McAfee SECURE™ scans the Discount School Supply website daily and, after it is determined the site is safe and secure, posts its seal of approval with the date of the last scan. Look for the McAfee SECURE™ seal the next time you place an order. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to 

[Webmaster@DiscountSchoolSupply.com](mailto:Webmaster@DiscountSchoolSupply.com) (Subject: Security Question). 

**Sharing Information**  
We do not share your personally-identifiable information with outside marketers except as described in this section. We may share your information with our partners to enhance your experience. (For example, through our partnerships with other companies, you may receive information or offers regarding products or services in which you have previously expressed an interest and/or selected promotional offers that may be of interest to you.) Excelligence’s partners include all Excelligence® affiliates as well as other selected companies with which Excelligence® or its affiliates have a business relationship. These selected businesses use commercially-strict standards for providing quality products and services, responding to your needs, and safeguarding customer information. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with our partners, please send an email to 

[noshare@excelligence.com](mailto:noshare@excelligence.com) (Subject: Do Not Share). 

In certain circumstances, we may share your information with service providers, such as PayPal, only when such access is necessary to provide operational or other support services. Those service providers agree to maintain confidentiality and security of your information. 

Excelligence® may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. In some instances, we may access or disclose your information to protect or defend our own legal rights, to guard against fraud, and/or to protect the safety and security of other customers/users. 

**Online Ad Serving**  
Excelligence® partners with third-party advertising service providers known as Ad Networks to distribute ads on our behalf across the Internet. To facilitate the delivery of advertisements that may be of particular interest to you, we permit Ad Networks to collect anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites using cookies and pixel tags (also called web beacons). No sensitive or personal information (including name, phone number, address, and email address) is collected or shared with Ad Networks by Excelligence® during this process. To find out more about how the networks manage the privacy of information in conjunction with delivering ads online, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating the Network Advertising Initiative website, which offers useful information about Ad Networks, including information about how to opt-out of their information collections. 

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our website and email programs may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of each website visited that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website. 

**Accessing Your Information**  
You can access your personal information (shipping and billing addresses, email address, order history, “favorites lists”) and make updates and changes at any time by clicking "Your Account" and logging in with your password. 

Alternatively, you can also request changes to your account by contacting our Customer Service representatives.

**“Opt-Out” of Receiving Promotional Emails and Materials**  
We try to provide you with the most relevant information about our latest email specials, sales notifications, educational events information, and other promotional messages. If you prefer to discontinue marketing communication from us, you can unsubscribe from our site’s email marketing list by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each promotional email. Please allow up to 10 days for your email address to be removed from our site’s email marketing list. 

In addition you can also unsubscribe from our site’s email marketing list by:  
sending a request to be removed from the mailing list via email to 

[CustomerService@DiscountSchoolSupply.com](mailto:CustomerService@DiscountSchoolSupply.com) (Subject: Email opt-out)  
sending a written request via mail to:  
Discount School Supply  
PO Box 6013  
Carol Stream IL 60197-6013 

**Notification of Changes**  
Excelligence reserves the right to change or modify/amend any of the terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy, or any policy of the site. Changes occur at the sole discretion of Excelligence and can be made without prior notice. Should Excelligence decide to change terms of its Privacy Policy or any other site policy, it will post a new version on the site. Any changes or modifications to these site terms will be effective upon posting of the revisions and will be clearly dated. Your continued use of the site following the posting of any changes or modifications constitutes your acceptance of such changes or modifications. You should frequently review these site terms and any other applicable policies, including their dates, to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of the site.
